Guide to the Women's Fund for Health Education and Resiliency (HER) Records 2000-002
University of Houston Libraries Special Collections
Women's Fund for Health Education and Resiliency (HER) Records
1979-2014
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
Women's Fund for Health Education and Resiliency
2000-002
40.00 Linear Feet
The Women's Fund for Health Education and Resiliency Records collection consists of 34 boxes of material, including fundraising and educational outreach events documentation, administrative materials, committee meeting minutes and files, correspondence, membership rosters, income tallies, research grant applications, photographs, newsletters, and publications.
Conditions Governing Access:
Open for research.
Acquisition Information:
The Women's Fund for Health Education and Research (HER) donated twelve record cartons in July 2000. Another contribution of four record cartons arrived in March 2002. An additional 23 boxes arrived on November 11, 2015. These included a signficant collection of digital material on CDs and floppy discs.
Historical Note:
The Women's Fund for Health Education and Resiliency was founded in February 1979 by Jacqueline and Wayne Goettsche with a seed endowment as the Women's Fund for Health Education and Research (HER). Concerned that women's health issues lacked appropriate funding and that research findings using only male subjects was applied indiscriminately to women, the Goettsches established the Women's Fund to support research on women's health issues and to disseminate women's health information through educational programs. The Goettsches organized a fundraising initiation barbeque in May 1979 that drew nearly 100 attendees from Houston's social and medical elite. With this event, the Women's Fund commemorated the signing of the Bylaws and officially launched the new organization.
As a non-profit foundation, the Women's Fund for HER has been dedicated to understanding, improving, and promoting women's health by providing support for research and educational programs. Fundraising through membership solicitation, special events, and corporate support is a primary goal of the Women's Fund. In 1979, the Women's Fund began with about 200 charter members; by 2001 membership had increased to 605, 203 of which are lifetime members. Membership categories include individual annual members, lifetime members, medical members, and corporate members.
The Women's Fund for HER hosts a variety of events each year; central among them is the Annual Benefit Luncheon held each fall. In 1983 the Women's Fund held its First Annual Benefit Luncheon with Erma Bombeck as the guest speaker. Featured speakers have included David Eisenhower, John Bradshaw, Suzanne Somers, and Liz Carpenter. Since 1991, the Women's Fund has presented the John P. McGovern Fall Seminar, which offers specialized information on topics such as allergies, chemical dependency, depression, and over-the-counter medicines. An Annual Spring Seminar provides another venue for similar kinds of information. The Program Committee organizes smaller and more frequent lecture/seminars throughout the year, often in collaboration with volunteers representing local medical institutions, and so many of the seminars are free. Membership coffees, held three to four times a year in a member's home, feature presentations on women's health concerns such as heart disease or alcoholism. Both Michael DeBakey and Ann Richards have spoken to attendees at these membership coffees.
As part of their educational outreach, the Women's Fund publishes A Primer on Women's Health, which is circulated to groups, agencies, and corporations without charge. To reach a wider audience, the Women's Fund translated the Primer into Spanish. Local philanthropic foundations and individuals support publication of the Primer. Another publication, Health Notes, helps women track their medical histories and maintain records of tests and diagnoses.
In addition to special events and the Primer, the Women's Fund has supported basic and clinical research related to women's health concerns. Between 1980 and 1992 the Women's Fund awarded 73 grants for medical research and services geared toward women's needs.
For more information, see: https://thewomensfund.org/
Physical Characteristics or Technical Requirements:
In addition to paper records, this collection contains digital archival materials. These can be accessed in the Special Collections Reading Room by advance request. Because portions of this collection are unprocessed, these materials may require up to two weeks to access. Some files may be restricted and not available for access at all. Contact curator Vince Lee (velee@uh.edu) for more information.
Scope and Contents
The Women's Fund for Health Education and Resiliency Records collection consists of 34 boxes of material, including fundraising and educational outreach events documentation, administrative materials, committee meeting minutes and files, correspondence, membership rosters, income tallies, research grant applications, photographs, newsletters, and publications. Arriving in two installments, the processed records date from 1979-2014 and were not interfiled. As a result, materials within each series are often housed in multiple locations throughout the collection.
The collection is organized topically into 12 series: Administration, Board of Trustees, Special Events, Granting Process, Gifts and Donations, Printing Samples, Publications, Photographs, Guest Books, Austin Office, and VHS Programs Library. The Special Events series is the largest and includes materials pertaining to annual benefit luncheons, McGovern fall seminars, spring seminars, and membership coffee/lectures. A few artifacts such as two guest books are also included. 5 1/4 inch floppy disks with newsletter files are also included -- please contact curator Vince Lee (velee@uh.edu) with questions about accessing these files.
Correspondence; Financial records; Newsletters; Rosters; Health education; Health education of women; Nonprofit organizations -- Texas -- Houston; Women's Fund for Health Education and Research; Women's Fund for Health Education and Resiliency
- Administration, 1979-2014
  Scope and Contents
  The Administration series includes documents related to the organizational and financial maintenance of the Women's Fund dating from its inauguration in 1979 through 2014. Materials including mission statement and organizational history, financial records and investments, non-profit status and management, correspondence, office management, and personnel and staff meeting minutes. Only moderate reorganization of the materials was necessary to establish cohesion among the documents incorporated into the Administration series.
  - Mission Statement and Organization History, 1980-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Articles of Incorporation and Bylaws, 1989-1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Financial Records, 1979-1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Financial Records, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Financial Records - Advertising, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Financial Records - Investments, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Non-Profit Status and Management, 1989-1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, 1992-1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Letters of Endorsement, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Philanthropic Status, 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Office Management and Equipment, 1967-1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Personnel, 1979-1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Saint Martin's Endowment, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 19a)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Women's Fund History: Articles of Incorporation, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - The Women's Fund History: What's it all about, post 1979, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Organization – Judy Allen, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - President's Note, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, Agenda, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, Minutes, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Program History, 1979 – 1989 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Long Range Planning Meeting Minutes, Organizational Structure and Mission Statement, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - By- Laws Revised/ Non- profit corporation, 1992- 1993 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Volunteer related meeting/ correspondence/ forms, 1992- 1993; 1995 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Volunteer Luncheon/ Letters, 1997; 2000 – 2001 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Intern/ Volunteer, University of Houston, 2009 – 2010 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Volunteer/ Intern Packets, 2009 – 2010 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Staff Timesheet/ Payroll Schedule, 2011 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Volunteer Awards/ Certificates, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Mileage Reimbursement Form, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - The Spitfire Strategies Smart Chart 2.0 Resource, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Logo Samples, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Handbook of Personnel Policies, 1987 – 1992 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - HHSC Internal Audit Division, 2011 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - The Women Fund for Female Enrichment Logo/ Design, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Website Notes/ Correspondence, 2011 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Website Restructure Chart, undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Procedures Manual, undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Board of Trustees Manual, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Rowenta, Home appliances, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Resource: Texas Association of Nonprofit Organizations Business Code, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Employment - Interview Questions, 2009 - 2010 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Policy/ Protocols Creation: Emails/ Correspondence, 2008 - 2009 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Kelly Young's Business Proposal, 2008 – 2010 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Audit & 990's – Email/ Correspondence, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Thank you Notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Funding History: Fundraiser, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Wedge Properties Management Corporation, 2009 – 2011 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Human Resource Personnel, 2000; 2005; 2009 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Admin Misc: Texas Sales and Tax exemption certification, Texas Board of examiner professional counselors, 2005; 2009 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Employment: Job Description and Thank you letters, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Employment: Organization Board Member, undated (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Binder - Logix Communications Manual (Box 15, Item 1)
  - Binder: Wedge Properties Management, Tenant Handbook, 2005; 2009 – 2010 (Box 15, Item 2)
  - City of Houston Proclamation (Box 15a)
  - Framed Certificate of Registration from CHEON, 1989 (Box 34, Item 2)
  - Framed Luncheon Committee Members List, undated (Box 34, Item 3)
  - Women and Girls Good Health Day Proclamations, 1993-1999 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Board of Trustees, 1979-2010
  All records of the activities of the Board of Trustees from 1979 through 1999 are collected in this series, which includes meeting minutes, correspondence, manual, and retreats.
  - Advisory Board Committee, 1979-1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Advisory Board Committee, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Advisory Board Member Profiles, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Corporate Advisory Board Committee, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 23a)
  - Endowment Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 23b)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 1979-1985 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence/Minutes, 1981-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence/Minutes, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence/Minutes, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence/Minutes, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence/Minutes, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence/Minutes, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence/Minutes, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence/Minutes, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 7a)
  - Board of Trustees Manual, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
  - Board of Trustees - Retreat, 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - President's Report, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 10a)
  - Foundation Development, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 10b)
  - The Women's Fund Board Profile (Blank), undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - By – Laws and Articles of Incorporation, Procedures manual, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Meeting, 1982-1995 (Box 19, Folder 3-16)
  - The Women's Fund: Executive Committee/ Board Meeting, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Women's Fund: President Report, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Executive Committee/ Board Meeting, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Board of Trustees Manual, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Board of Trustees, Nominating Committee, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Board of Trustees, Manual, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Board of Trustees, Nominating Committee, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Membership Committee, Articles, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - The Women's Funds: Board of Trustees Meeting, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Board Manual Updates, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - President's Report, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Board of Trustees Manual, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Standing Committee, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Board of Trustee, Executive Committee Meeting, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Draft -The Magnitude of Sexual Assault in Texas (report), 2007 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Board of Trustees Manuals, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Trustees Program/ Proposal, 2007 – 2008 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - The Magnitude of Sexual Assault in Texas (report), Research materials, 2007 – 2008 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Board Meeting Email Correspondence, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Board of Trustees, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Board Retreat and Meeting, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - President's Reports, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Fundraisers, Letter Draft: Annual Membership coffee, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Receipt's, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Board Info/ by- laws, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Annual Campaigns, 2003 -2005 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Advisory Board, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Long Range Planning, email correspondence, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Board Meetings: The Consent Agenda, Board Source, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Philanthropy, A new Breed, Article, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Houston Area Women's Center, Finance Committee, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, Minutes, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Agency History, Barbs Questions, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Memberships, 2000 – 2001; 2003- 2004 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, Minutes, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes & Memorandums, 1987; 1990 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Yearbook, Play 1, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Kids Fox Update, Week 19, Email Correspondence, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Publication Report, Women and Health, 2003 – 2006 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Corporate Support/ Members List, 1995 – 1998 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Leaders Circle Agenda #4, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Memberships Memorandums, Retrieved Folders, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Nonprofit Development Survey, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - JP Morgan Chase Folder Profile, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Folder: The Women's Fun: Brochures Samples, 1991-1992; 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Membership, Letter, and Directory, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Better Business Bureau Report, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - The Women's Fund, Board of Trustees Manual, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Health Literacy Instruction Guide, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Kelsey- Seybold Clinic, Ann Cook, Board Retreat Notes, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Board of Trustees, Meeting Minutes, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - The Women's Fund for H.E.R Foundation: Board of Trustees Meeting, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Board of Trustees Bio's, 1979 – 1988 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Board Meetings, Memorandum, Audit Procedures, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Board Meeting, Table Purchases in 2004, Miscellaneous Events, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Board Meeting: Leaderships and Board Retreat/ Email Correspondence, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous, Luncheon Planning/ Email Correspondence, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Board of Trustees and Nominees Applications, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - By- Laws Elections, Beneficiary Trustees, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous Even/ Email Correspondence, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Long Range Planning, Task Force/ Email Correspondence, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Long Range Planning, Email Correspondence, Meeting Agenda & Notes, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - The Women's Fund: Executive Committee Agenda, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - YMCA of Greater Houston (ideas to grow luncheon), 2005 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Board of Trustees, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Annual Joint Meeting: Board of Trustees & Advisory Board, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Board of Trustees Agenda, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Gateway to Care Correspondence, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Board of Trustees Manual, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Board of Trustees Profiles, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Program Proposal, Women's Health and Advocacy Project, undated (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Women of Distinction: Harriet Latimer, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Outreach Planning, undated (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Nominating Committee Letters, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Long Range Plan, 2002-2004 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Long Range Plan, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Long Range Plan 2005-2008 Draft (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Public Record; Exempt Organization Return, 2008-2009 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Board Meeting, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Email/Correspondence; Federal Minimum Wage Update, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Budget Overview/Finances, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Statements, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2000; 2003-2004 (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Notes to the 2009 Budget, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Budget Changes Email Correspondence, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Benefit Report by Last Name, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Proposal?, undated (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Houston's Women Center Strategic Plan, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Planning Budget/ Financials, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Budget/Financials, Program, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - Board Member Bio, undated (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Financials; 2009-2010 Budget (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - Chevron Houston Marathon, undated (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - Transaction Details by Account, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Personal Email Information Email Correspondence, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - Membership Tickets, 2011 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Karen Lee & Company –Service Offer Details, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Philanthropy Article/ Miscellaneous Documents, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Membership, 2011 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Women of Distinction Nominee, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Membership Directories, 1990-1996 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - PPPC Hotel Reservation Meeting, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Baylor College of Medicine Monthly Financial Report, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Financial –Check Register, 2000-2008 (Box 21, Folder 9-17)
  - Essays, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Executive Committee Resignation, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Board Member Nomination/ Application, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Personal Committee Meeting-Job Applications Complete, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Personal Committee Meeting, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Y yo que? Una Guia de Salud para Jovencitas, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Financial- Primer Copyright Information, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Fund Board Profile, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Fund Board Profile, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Fund Board member Nomination/Application, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Laura Lee Blanton Personal Biography –Immediate Press Release, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Board Member Nomination/Application, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Board Member Nomination/ Application, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Preparation of an Executive Committee Manual, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - The National Women's Health Week Seminar Luncheon, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Statement of Financial Position, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Registrant List, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Executive Board Position, Email Correspondence, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Volunteer/ Internship –Completed Application, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Personnel Policies, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Board Member Nomination/ Application, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Board Member Nomination/ Application, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Memorandum- Board Profile Form, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Personal Committee Analysis, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Assessment Form Memorandum, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Executive Director Position –Email Correspondence, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Blackbaud e Tapestry User's Agreement, 2012 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Healthy and Human Services Commission, 2011 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Executive Director Position –Email Correspondence, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Northern Trust Transfer, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Executive Director Candidates Not Selected, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Board Meeting, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Corporate Health Education Program (CHEP), 2001 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, Financial Summaries, 1979-1989 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Marketing Plan for Notecards, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Committee Records, 1979-2011
  The Committee Records series documents committee activity within the organization including committees with a short life span and committees that have endured since the organization's inception in 1979. Materials include lists of standing committees plus minutes and correspondence for development, long range planning, membership, newsletter, nominating, program, public relations, volunteer, and ways and means committees. Documents relating to committees as well as the committees' products, such as newsletters, are included in this series. Folder arrangement begins with a folder of documents on the formation and maintenance of various committees and continues with specific committees in alphabetical order. Folders within a particular committee are arranged chronologically.
  - Standing Committees, 1984-1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Community Focus Committee, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Community Outreach Committee, 2003-2011
    - The Women's Fund – Scholarship Essay, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - The Women's Fund – Publication Order Forms, 2009-2010 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - The Women's Fund – Community Outreach Committee Meeting, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - National Women's Health Week Survey, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - The Women's Fund – Kelsey Seybold Clinic (at Houston Center), undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - The Women's Fund – Community Outreach Committee Meeting, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 8)